- Okay, my turn. Let me talk to him.
- Go ahead.
(Sheldon:)2311 North Los Robles Avenue...
(Sheldon:)...Pasadena, California
to International Space Station.
(Sheldon:)Can you read me? Over.
(Howard:)Yes, I read you, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Copy that. Over.
- What are you doing?
- I'm talking to a man in space.
(Sheldon:)If you don't have the...
(Sheldon:)...he might as well be at the Coffee Bean
over on Lake Street.
You're out of your mind, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)That's a negative.
My mother had me tested. Over.
Come on, scrub-a-dub, Loops.
(Howard:)All right. All right. I gotta go.
(Howard:)There's a meteor shower.
Wanna see a meteor shower?
(Mike:)Take a look at what Dimitri
just left you in the toilet.
- Bye.
- Over and out.
(Raj:)Bye, buddy!
(Amy:)- Hello?
- Hey, Stuart, come on in.